[{"subjectID":"h0q02yk7eu","prolificID":"6640ebff6fd8319ba014acb0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677423c7cc61b67917d254b3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664951451,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":0,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"200","question":"Do you have a favorite food or cuisine? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":15466,"timeElapsed":249389},{"subjectID":"h0q02yk7eu","prolificID":"6640ebff6fd8319ba014acb0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677423c7cc61b67917d254b3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665007331,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":1,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"200","question":"Do you have a favorite food or cuisine? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":52,"rt":55877,"timeElapsed":305270},{"subjectID":"h0q02yk7eu","prolificID":"6640ebff6fd8319ba014acb0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677423c7cc61b67917d254b3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665021607,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":2,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"200","question":"Do you have a favorite food or cuisine? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":77,"rt":14271,"timeElapsed":319546},{"subjectID":"h0q02yk7eu","prolificID":"6640ebff6fd8319ba014acb0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677423c7cc61b67917d254b3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665031316,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":3,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"200","question":"Do you have a favorite food or cuisine? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":9704,"timeElapsed":329255},{"subjectID":"h0q02yk7eu","prolificID":"6640ebff6fd8319ba014acb0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677423c7cc61b67917d254b3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665035907,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":4,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"200","question":"Do you have a favorite food or cuisine? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":43,"rt":4586,"timeElapsed":333845},{"subjectID":"h0q02yk7eu","prolificID":"6640ebff6fd8319ba014acb0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677423c7cc61b67917d254b3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665039182,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":5,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"200","question":"Do you have a favorite food or cuisine? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":78,"rt":3274,"timeElapsed":337121},{"subjectID":"h0q02yk7eu","prolificID":"6640ebff6fd8319ba014acb0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677423c7cc61b67917d254b3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665044037,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":6,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"200","question":"Do you have a favorite food or cuisine? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":29,"rt":4850,"timeElapsed":341976},{"subjectID":"h0q02yk7eu","prolificID":"6640ebff6fd8319ba014acb0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677423c7cc61b67917d254b3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665100960,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":7,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"200","question":"Do you have a favorite food or cuisine? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":44,"rt":56917,"timeElapsed":398899},{"subjectID":"h0q02yk7eu","prolificID":"6640ebff6fd8319ba014acb0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677423c7cc61b67917d254b3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665114871,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":8,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"200","question":"Do you have a favorite food or cuisine? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":52,"rt":13907,"timeElapsed":412810},{"subjectID":"h0q02yk7eu","prolificID":"6640ebff6fd8319ba014acb0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677423c7cc61b67917d254b3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665149903,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":9,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"165","question":"Do you subscribe to any magazines or read online articles from any magazines? Which ones have you subscribed to or read regularly in the past?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":75,"rt":32920,"timeElapsed":447842},{"subjectID":"h0q02yk7eu","prolificID":"6640ebff6fd8319ba014acb0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677423c7cc61b67917d254b3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665209129,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":10,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"165","question":"Do you subscribe to any magazines or read online articles from any magazines? Which ones have you subscribed to or read regularly in the past?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":77,"rt":59224,"timeElapsed":507068},{"subjectID":"h0q02yk7eu","prolificID":"6640ebff6fd8319ba014acb0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677423c7cc61b67917d254b3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665222448,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":11,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"165","question":"Do you subscribe to any magazines or read online articles from any magazines? Which ones have you subscribed to or read regularly in the past?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":76,"rt":13314,"timeElapsed":520387},{"subjectID":"h0q02yk7eu","prolificID":"6640ebff6fd8319ba014acb0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677423c7cc61b67917d254b3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665273265,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":12,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"165","question":"Do you subscribe to any magazines or read online articles from any magazines? Which ones have you subscribed to or read regularly in the past?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":66,"rt":50813,"timeElapsed":571204},{"subjectID":"h0q02yk7eu","prolificID":"6640ebff6fd8319ba014acb0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677423c7cc61b67917d254b3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665280043,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":13,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"165","question":"Do you subscribe to any magazines or read online articles from any magazines? Which ones have you subscribed to or read regularly in the past?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":6775,"timeElapsed":577981},{"subjectID":"h0q02yk7eu","prolificID":"6640ebff6fd8319ba014acb0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677423c7cc61b67917d254b3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665284163,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":14,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"165","question":"Do you subscribe to any magazines or read online articles from any magazines? Which ones have you subscribed to or read regularly in the past?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":80,"rt":4116,"timeElapsed":582102},{"subjectID":"h0q02yk7eu","prolificID":"6640ebff6fd8319ba014acb0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677423c7cc61b67917d254b3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665290244,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":15,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"165","question":"Do you subscribe to any magazines or read online articles from any magazines? Which ones have you subscribed to or read regularly in the past?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":26,"rt":6078,"timeElapsed":588183},{"subjectID":"h0q02yk7eu","prolificID":"6640ebff6fd8319ba014acb0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677423c7cc61b67917d254b3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665296004,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":16,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"165","question":"Do you subscribe to any magazines or read online articles from any magazines? Which ones have you subscribed to or read regularly in the past?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":54,"rt":5757,"timeElapsed":593943},{"subjectID":"h0q02yk7eu","prolificID":"6640ebff6fd8319ba014acb0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677423c7cc61b67917d254b3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665309615,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":17,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"165","question":"Do you subscribe to any magazines or read online articles from any magazines? Which ones have you subscribed to or read regularly in the past?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":54,"rt":13607,"timeElapsed":607554},{"subjectID":"h0q02yk7eu","prolificID":"6640ebff6fd8319ba014acb0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677423c7cc61b67917d254b3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665340215,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":18,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"42","question":"What is your favorite trait about yourself and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":76,"rt":27975,"timeElapsed":638154},{"subjectID":"h0q02yk7eu","prolificID":"6640ebff6fd8319ba014acb0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677423c7cc61b67917d254b3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665371765,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":19,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"42","question":"What is your favorite trait about yourself and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":76,"rt":31545,"timeElapsed":669703},{"subjectID":"h0q02yk7eu","prolificID":"6640ebff6fd8319ba014acb0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677423c7cc61b67917d254b3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665379037,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":20,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"42","question":"What is your favorite trait about yourself and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":73,"rt":7269,"timeElapsed":676976},{"subjectID":"h0q02yk7eu","prolificID":"6640ebff6fd8319ba014acb0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677423c7cc61b67917d254b3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665381855,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":21,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"42","question":"What is your favorite trait about yourself and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":75,"rt":2814,"timeElapsed":679793},{"subjectID":"h0q02yk7eu","prolificID":"6640ebff6fd8319ba014acb0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677423c7cc61b67917d254b3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665387499,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":22,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"42","question":"What is your favorite trait about yourself and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":77,"rt":5641,"timeElapsed":685438},{"subjectID":"h0q02yk7eu","prolificID":"6640ebff6fd8319ba014acb0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677423c7cc61b67917d254b3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665392866,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":23,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"42","question":"What is your favorite trait about yourself and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":75,"rt":5362,"timeElapsed":690804},{"subjectID":"h0q02yk7eu","prolificID":"6640ebff6fd8319ba014acb0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677423c7cc61b67917d254b3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665397878,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":24,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"42","question":"What is your favorite trait about yourself and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":5006,"timeElapsed":695817},{"subjectID":"h0q02yk7eu","prolificID":"6640ebff6fd8319ba014acb0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677423c7cc61b67917d254b3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665457494,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":25,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"42","question":"What is your favorite trait about yourself and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":59614,"timeElapsed":755433},{"subjectID":"h0q02yk7eu","prolificID":"6640ebff6fd8319ba014acb0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677423c7cc61b67917d254b3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665477847,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":26,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"42","question":"What is your favorite trait about yourself and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":20351,"timeElapsed":775786},{"subjectID":"h0q02yk7eu","prolificID":"6640ebff6fd8319ba014acb0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677423c7cc61b67917d254b3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665486862,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":100,"trialIdx":26,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"What is your favorite trait about yourself and why?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled HAMBURGER","scaleTextMin":"HOTDOG","scaleTextMax":"HAMBURGER","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":9013,"timeElapsed":784801},{"subjectID":"h0q02yk7eu","prolificID":"6640ebff6fd8319ba014acb0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677423c7cc61b67917d254b3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665500624,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":27,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"101","question":"If you could erase one memory from your mind, what would it be and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":81,"rt":12050,"timeElapsed":798563},{"subjectID":"h0q02yk7eu","prolificID":"6640ebff6fd8319ba014acb0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677423c7cc61b67917d254b3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665504790,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":28,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"101","question":"If you could erase one memory from your mind, what would it be and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":84,"rt":4163,"timeElapsed":802729},{"subjectID":"h0q02yk7eu","prolificID":"6640ebff6fd8319ba014acb0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677423c7cc61b67917d254b3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665534014,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":29,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"101","question":"If you could erase one memory from your mind, what would it be and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":71,"rt":29213,"timeElapsed":831953},{"subjectID":"h0q02yk7eu","prolificID":"6640ebff6fd8319ba014acb0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677423c7cc61b67917d254b3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665558711,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":30,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"101","question":"If you could erase one memory from your mind, what would it be and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":77,"rt":24693,"timeElapsed":856649},{"subjectID":"h0q02yk7eu","prolificID":"6640ebff6fd8319ba014acb0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677423c7cc61b67917d254b3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665585010,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":31,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"101","question":"If you could erase one memory from your mind, what would it be and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":82,"rt":26297,"timeElapsed":882949},{"subjectID":"h0q02yk7eu","prolificID":"6640ebff6fd8319ba014acb0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677423c7cc61b67917d254b3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665588102,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":32,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"101","question":"If you could erase one memory from your mind, what would it be and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":83,"rt":3089,"timeElapsed":886041},{"subjectID":"h0q02yk7eu","prolificID":"6640ebff6fd8319ba014acb0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677423c7cc61b67917d254b3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665594663,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":33,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"101","question":"If you could erase one memory from your mind, what would it be and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":89,"rt":6557,"timeElapsed":892602},{"subjectID":"h0q02yk7eu","prolificID":"6640ebff6fd8319ba014acb0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677423c7cc61b67917d254b3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665601991,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":34,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"101","question":"If you could erase one memory from your mind, what would it be and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":7323,"timeElapsed":899930},{"subjectID":"h0q02yk7eu","prolificID":"6640ebff6fd8319ba014acb0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677423c7cc61b67917d254b3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665606951,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":35,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"101","question":"If you could erase one memory from your mind, what would it be and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":4956,"timeElapsed":904890},{"subjectID":"h0q02yk7eu","prolificID":"6640ebff6fd8319ba014acb0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677423c7cc61b67917d254b3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665624173,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":36,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"196","question":"What was your favorite board game growing up or currently?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":73,"rt":15445,"timeElapsed":922112},{"subjectID":"h0q02yk7eu","prolificID":"6640ebff6fd8319ba014acb0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677423c7cc61b67917d254b3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665630591,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":37,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"196","question":"What was your favorite board game growing up or currently?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":71,"rt":6413,"timeElapsed":928530},{"subjectID":"h0q02yk7eu","prolificID":"6640ebff6fd8319ba014acb0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677423c7cc61b67917d254b3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665634747,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":38,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"196","question":"What was your favorite board game growing up or currently?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":69,"rt":4152,"timeElapsed":932686},{"subjectID":"h0q02yk7eu","prolificID":"6640ebff6fd8319ba014acb0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677423c7cc61b67917d254b3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665641186,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":39,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"196","question":"What was your favorite board game growing up or currently?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":71,"rt":6435,"timeElapsed":939125},{"subjectID":"h0q02yk7eu","prolificID":"6640ebff6fd8319ba014acb0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677423c7cc61b67917d254b3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665648096,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":40,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"196","question":"What was your favorite board game growing up or currently?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":6907,"timeElapsed":946035},{"subjectID":"h0q02yk7eu","prolificID":"6640ebff6fd8319ba014acb0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677423c7cc61b67917d254b3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665661940,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":41,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"196","question":"What was your favorite board game growing up or currently?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":13842,"timeElapsed":959879},{"subjectID":"h0q02yk7eu","prolificID":"6640ebff6fd8319ba014acb0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677423c7cc61b67917d254b3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665668341,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":42,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"196","question":"What was your favorite board game growing up or currently?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":6397,"timeElapsed":966279},{"subjectID":"h0q02yk7eu","prolificID":"6640ebff6fd8319ba014acb0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677423c7cc61b67917d254b3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665673807,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":43,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"196","question":"What was your favorite board game growing up or currently?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":65,"rt":5463,"timeElapsed":971746},{"subjectID":"h0q02yk7eu","prolificID":"6640ebff6fd8319ba014acb0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677423c7cc61b67917d254b3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665679253,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":44,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"196","question":"What was your favorite board game growing up or currently?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":5438,"timeElapsed":977192},{"subjectID":"h0q02yk7eu","prolificID":"6640ebff6fd8319ba014acb0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677423c7cc61b67917d254b3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665698765,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":45,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"113","question":"Who are the most important people in your life right now? Has this changed over time?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":82,"rt":18016,"timeElapsed":996704},{"subjectID":"h0q02yk7eu","prolificID":"6640ebff6fd8319ba014acb0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677423c7cc61b67917d254b3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665703806,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":46,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"113","question":"Who are the most important people in your life right now? Has this changed over time?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":5038,"timeElapsed":1001745},{"subjectID":"h0q02yk7eu","prolificID":"6640ebff6fd8319ba014acb0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677423c7cc61b67917d254b3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665707662,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":47,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"113","question":"Who are the most important people in your life right now? Has this changed over time?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":73,"rt":3853,"timeElapsed":1005601},{"subjectID":"h0q02yk7eu","prolificID":"6640ebff6fd8319ba014acb0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677423c7cc61b67917d254b3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665711933,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":48,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"113","question":"Who are the most important people in your life right now? Has this changed over time?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":69,"rt":4268,"timeElapsed":1009872},{"subjectID":"h0q02yk7eu","prolificID":"6640ebff6fd8319ba014acb0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677423c7cc61b67917d254b3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665718666,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":49,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"113","question":"Who are the most important people in your life right now? Has this changed over time?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":6730,"timeElapsed":1016605},{"subjectID":"h0q02yk7eu","prolificID":"6640ebff6fd8319ba014acb0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677423c7cc61b67917d254b3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665742249,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":50,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"113","question":"Who are the most important people in your life right now? Has this changed over time?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":48,"rt":23579,"timeElapsed":1040188},{"subjectID":"h0q02yk7eu","prolificID":"6640ebff6fd8319ba014acb0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677423c7cc61b67917d254b3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665758341,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":51,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"113","question":"Who are the most important people in your life right now? Has this changed over time?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":16090,"timeElapsed":1056280},{"subjectID":"h0q02yk7eu","prolificID":"6640ebff6fd8319ba014acb0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677423c7cc61b67917d254b3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665762829,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":52,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"113","question":"Who are the most important people in your life right now? Has this changed over time?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":4485,"timeElapsed":1060768},{"subjectID":"h0q02yk7eu","prolificID":"6640ebff6fd8319ba014acb0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677423c7cc61b67917d254b3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665767501,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":53,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"113","question":"Who are the most important people in your life right now? Has this changed over time?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":4667,"timeElapsed":1065440},{"subjectID":"h0q02yk7eu","prolificID":"6640ebff6fd8319ba014acb0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677423c7cc61b67917d254b3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665798995,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":54,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"82","question":"What quality in people do you find most enviable?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":66,"rt":27390,"timeElapsed":1096934},{"subjectID":"h0q02yk7eu","prolificID":"6640ebff6fd8319ba014acb0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677423c7cc61b67917d254b3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665802246,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":55,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"82","question":"What quality in people do you find most enviable?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":70,"rt":3246,"timeElapsed":1100185},{"subjectID":"h0q02yk7eu","prolificID":"6640ebff6fd8319ba014acb0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677423c7cc61b67917d254b3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665806647,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":56,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"82","question":"What quality in people do you find most enviable?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":4398,"timeElapsed":1104586},{"subjectID":"h0q02yk7eu","prolificID":"6640ebff6fd8319ba014acb0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677423c7cc61b67917d254b3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665811636,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":57,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"82","question":"What quality in people do you find most enviable?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":4984,"timeElapsed":1109575},{"subjectID":"h0q02yk7eu","prolificID":"6640ebff6fd8319ba014acb0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677423c7cc61b67917d254b3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665818793,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":58,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"82","question":"What quality in people do you find most enviable?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":7153,"timeElapsed":1116732},{"subjectID":"h0q02yk7eu","prolificID":"6640ebff6fd8319ba014acb0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677423c7cc61b67917d254b3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665824002,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":59,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"82","question":"What quality in people do you find most enviable?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":39,"rt":5205,"timeElapsed":1121941},{"subjectID":"h0q02yk7eu","prolificID":"6640ebff6fd8319ba014acb0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677423c7cc61b67917d254b3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665829648,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":60,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"82","question":"What quality in people do you find most enviable?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":33,"rt":5642,"timeElapsed":1127586},{"subjectID":"h0q02yk7eu","prolificID":"6640ebff6fd8319ba014acb0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677423c7cc61b67917d254b3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665840307,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":61,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"82","question":"What quality in people do you find most enviable?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":65,"rt":10653,"timeElapsed":1138246},{"subjectID":"h0q02yk7eu","prolificID":"6640ebff6fd8319ba014acb0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677423c7cc61b67917d254b3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665844474,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":62,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"82","question":"What quality in people do you find most enviable?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":4165,"timeElapsed":1142413},{"subjectID":"h0q02yk7eu","prolificID":"6640ebff6fd8319ba014acb0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677423c7cc61b67917d254b3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665854025,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":63,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"169","question":"Have you ever had a nickname? How did you get it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":70,"rt":7970,"timeElapsed":1151964},{"subjectID":"h0q02yk7eu","prolificID":"6640ebff6fd8319ba014acb0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677423c7cc61b67917d254b3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665858524,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":64,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"169","question":"Have you ever had a nickname? How did you get it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":69,"rt":4495,"timeElapsed":1156462},{"subjectID":"h0q02yk7eu","prolificID":"6640ebff6fd8319ba014acb0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677423c7cc61b67917d254b3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665873069,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":65,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"169","question":"Have you ever had a nickname? How did you get it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":14542,"timeElapsed":1171008},{"subjectID":"h0q02yk7eu","prolificID":"6640ebff6fd8319ba014acb0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677423c7cc61b67917d254b3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665878244,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":66,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"169","question":"Have you ever had a nickname? How did you get it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":5172,"timeElapsed":1176183},{"subjectID":"h0q02yk7eu","prolificID":"6640ebff6fd8319ba014acb0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677423c7cc61b67917d254b3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665882825,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":67,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"169","question":"Have you ever had a nickname? How did you get it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":4579,"timeElapsed":1180764},{"subjectID":"h0q02yk7eu","prolificID":"6640ebff6fd8319ba014acb0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677423c7cc61b67917d254b3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665909596,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":68,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"169","question":"Have you ever had a nickname? How did you get it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":48,"rt":26769,"timeElapsed":1207535},{"subjectID":"h0q02yk7eu","prolificID":"6640ebff6fd8319ba014acb0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677423c7cc61b67917d254b3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665924115,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":69,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"169","question":"Have you ever had a nickname? How did you get it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":42,"rt":14517,"timeElapsed":1222054},{"subjectID":"h0q02yk7eu","prolificID":"6640ebff6fd8319ba014acb0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677423c7cc61b67917d254b3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665929157,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":70,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"169","question":"Have you ever had a nickname? How did you get it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":5039,"timeElapsed":1227095},{"subjectID":"h0q02yk7eu","prolificID":"6640ebff6fd8319ba014acb0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677423c7cc61b67917d254b3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665933698,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":71,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"169","question":"Have you ever had a nickname? How did you get it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":4538,"timeElapsed":1231637},{"subjectID":"h0q02yk7eu","prolificID":"6640ebff6fd8319ba014acb0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677423c7cc61b67917d254b3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665941417,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":72,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"55","question":"What do you think is the purpose of education?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":5818,"timeElapsed":1239356},{"subjectID":"h0q02yk7eu","prolificID":"6640ebff6fd8319ba014acb0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677423c7cc61b67917d254b3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665949052,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":73,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"55","question":"What do you think is the purpose of education?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":70,"rt":7632,"timeElapsed":1246991},{"subjectID":"h0q02yk7eu","prolificID":"6640ebff6fd8319ba014acb0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677423c7cc61b67917d254b3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665953787,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":74,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"55","question":"What do you think is the purpose of education?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":68,"rt":4732,"timeElapsed":1251726},{"subjectID":"h0q02yk7eu","prolificID":"6640ebff6fd8319ba014acb0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677423c7cc61b67917d254b3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665957252,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":75,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"55","question":"What do you think is the purpose of education?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":68,"rt":3457,"timeElapsed":1255191},{"subjectID":"h0q02yk7eu","prolificID":"6640ebff6fd8319ba014acb0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677423c7cc61b67917d254b3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665963287,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":76,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"55","question":"What do you think is the purpose of education?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":79,"rt":6032,"timeElapsed":1261226},{"subjectID":"h0q02yk7eu","prolificID":"6640ebff6fd8319ba014acb0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677423c7cc61b67917d254b3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665971646,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":77,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"55","question":"What do you think is the purpose of education?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":72,"rt":8354,"timeElapsed":1269584},{"subjectID":"h0q02yk7eu","prolificID":"6640ebff6fd8319ba014acb0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677423c7cc61b67917d254b3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665978779,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":78,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"55","question":"What do you think is the purpose of education?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":38,"rt":7130,"timeElapsed":1276718},{"subjectID":"h0q02yk7eu","prolificID":"6640ebff6fd8319ba014acb0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677423c7cc61b67917d254b3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665985604,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":79,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"55","question":"What do you think is the purpose of education?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":6823,"timeElapsed":1283543},{"subjectID":"h0q02yk7eu","prolificID":"6640ebff6fd8319ba014acb0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677423c7cc61b67917d254b3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665991466,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":0,"trialIdx":79,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"What do you think is the purpose of education?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMin":"STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMax":"PINEAPPLE","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":5858,"timeElapsed":1289404},{"subjectID":"h0q02yk7eu","prolificID":"6640ebff6fd8319ba014acb0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677423c7cc61b67917d254b3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665998165,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":80,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"55","question":"What do you think is the purpose of education?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":6695,"timeElapsed":1296104},{"subjectID":"h0q02yk7eu","prolificID":"6640ebff6fd8319ba014acb0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677423c7cc61b67917d254b3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735666012936,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":81,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"181","question":"What is your earliest memory? Do you know how old you were in this memory?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":33,"rt":12363,"timeElapsed":1310874},{"subjectID":"h0q02yk7eu","prolificID":"6640ebff6fd8319ba014acb0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677423c7cc61b67917d254b3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735666019280,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":82,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"181","question":"What is your earliest memory? Do you know how old you were in this memory?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":45,"rt":6342,"timeElapsed":1317219},{"subjectID":"h0q02yk7eu","prolificID":"6640ebff6fd8319ba014acb0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677423c7cc61b67917d254b3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735666031407,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":83,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"181","question":"What is your earliest memory? Do you know how old you were in this memory?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":51,"rt":12125,"timeElapsed":1329346},{"subjectID":"h0q02yk7eu","prolificID":"6640ebff6fd8319ba014acb0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677423c7cc61b67917d254b3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735666035995,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":84,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"181","question":"What is your earliest memory? Do you know how old you were in this memory?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":4586,"timeElapsed":1333934},{"subjectID":"h0q02yk7eu","prolificID":"6640ebff6fd8319ba014acb0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677423c7cc61b67917d254b3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735666044275,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":85,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"181","question":"What is your earliest memory? Do you know how old you were in this memory?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":8278,"timeElapsed":1342214},{"subjectID":"h0q02yk7eu","prolificID":"6640ebff6fd8319ba014acb0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677423c7cc61b67917d254b3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735666047986,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":86,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"181","question":"What is your earliest memory? Do you know how old you were in this memory?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":3707,"timeElapsed":1345925},{"subjectID":"h0q02yk7eu","prolificID":"6640ebff6fd8319ba014acb0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677423c7cc61b67917d254b3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735666052052,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":87,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"181","question":"What is your earliest memory? Do you know how old you were in this memory?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":40,"rt":4062,"timeElapsed":1349991},{"subjectID":"h0q02yk7eu","prolificID":"6640ebff6fd8319ba014acb0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677423c7cc61b67917d254b3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735666055717,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":88,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"181","question":"What is your earliest memory? Do you know how old you were in this memory?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":39,"rt":3662,"timeElapsed":1353656},{"subjectID":"h0q02yk7eu","prolificID":"6640ebff6fd8319ba014acb0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677423c7cc61b67917d254b3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735666058487,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":89,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"181","question":"What is your earliest memory? Do you know how old you were in this memory?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":36,"rt":2766,"timeElapsed":1356426}]